<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aristosvo.github.io</title>
    <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on aristosvo.github.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 19:40:39 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aristosvo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Defining Moments of 2020 2: A problem is not a problem</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/definining-moments-2020-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 19:40:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/definining-moments-2020-two/</guid>
      <description>During my stay on Lesbos, Greece, I lived in a house with a group of 12 people. One of the things I like in life as much as living the life itself is helping others. I don&amp;rsquo;t realise that most of the time, as most of the time (like most people) I&amp;rsquo;m busy working and living the live we think we are supposed to be living.
The moment that I want to highlight is the moment when one of my housemates had put parts of a melon in a glass bottle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Defining Moments of 2020 1: Encouragement is free!</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/definining-moments-2020-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 19:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/definining-moments-2020-one/</guid>
      <description>One of the moments that defined 2020 for me is actually a series of moments. It was part of my remote working experience on Lesbos, Greece. During that stay I worked remote for my employer in The Netherlands, but shared an office with one of the coordinators for Boat Refugee Foundation. She just started with that job, and I saw her pick up the job with an incredible energy. She definitely outperformed expectations, but at the same time she was trying to find her place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributing to the Azure Terraform provider</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/contributing-to-the-azure-terraform-provider/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:32:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/contributing-to-the-azure-terraform-provider/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I wanted to write about for a long time now is how to start contributing to open source. In my case it&amp;rsquo;s mostly contributing to the Azure Terraform provider. This is mostly related to my work as a Cloud Platform Engineer, but I think you could apply the lessons learned to a lot of open source communities.
They are put in a random order, maybe some of them are not relevant in your situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Werken bij VX Company: Cloud Platform Engineer [Dutch]</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/werken-bij-vx-company-als-cloud-platform-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 00:13:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/werken-bij-vx-company-als-cloud-platform-engineer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 14:06:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>It is a well known fact that everybody has somebody to share.
This is my blog: let&amp;rsquo;s try to share some stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authenticating Spring Boot apps on AKS with MSI</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/aks-with-msi-from-your-java-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 14:06:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/aks-with-msi-from-your-java-services/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was looking for the best solution to connect to Azure services for a few pods within Azure Kubernetes Service. These services are build with Spring Boot and my first idea was to only connect to Azure KeyVault. Along the way I discovered the awesomeness of Managed Service Identities and extended it to another Azure Service, Azure Storage.
Managed Service Identities: a short intro To explain a bit about Managed Service Identities I prefer to point towards the Azure docs:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commandline tricks: Get your Azure Kubernetes Clusters kubeconfig</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/azure-from-the-commandline-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:36:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/azure-from-the-commandline-2/</guid>
      <description>One of the subjects I wanted to touch on this blog is my journey in my new job. And with my new job a new cloud adventure started. In my previous job I was primarily focussed on IBM Cloud, AWS and a bit of Google Cloud. Although all clouds are in some way the same, there are also a lot of difficulties, hick-ups and new ideas marching around the corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commandline tricks: Switching between Azure Subscriptions</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/azure-from-the-commandline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:36:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/azure-from-the-commandline/</guid>
      <description>One of the subjects I wanted to touch on this blog is my journey in my new job. And with my new job a new cloud adventure started. In my previous job I was primarily focussed on IBM Cloud, AWS and a bit of Google Cloud. Although all clouds are in some way the same, there are also a lot of difficulties, hick-ups and new ideas marching around the corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 21:19:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>While I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot about writing my thoughts down a lot over the years, it never really happened. And although it is now happening, I&amp;rsquo;m still looking which direction to take. My first blog posts will probably focus on my journey, discoveries, tips and tricks from my job experiences and a lot of other stuff you&amp;rsquo;re probably not interested in. However, if you are and want me to know that, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://aristosvo.github.io/curriculum_vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aristosvo.github.io/curriculum_vitae/</guid>
      <description>Education  2014-2016 MSc, Biomedical Engineering; Rijksuniversiteit Groningen (Groningen) 2009-2014 BSc, Biomedical Engineering; Rijksuniversiteit Groningen (Groningen)  Experience Cloud Engineer @VX Company: (2019-now)
As a Cloud Engineer/DevOps Engineer we took care of a number of clients, all different in size and with different programming languages. Improvements we made during 2020 were:
  Implementation of Infrastructure as Code with Terraform
  Improvements for our clients on Kubernetes by standardizing on shared components</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
